Hear The Music. Feel The Beat.
Make It Happen is a music, romance, drama film directed by Darren Grant.
Embarking on a journey to fulfill her dreams as a dancer, a young girl discovers a new style
of dance that will prove to be the source of both conflict and self-discovery.
Lauryn Kirk, played by Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
Russ, played by Riley Smith.
Joel, played by John Reardon.
Dana, played by Tessa Thompson.
Brooke, played by Ashley Roberts.
Carmen, played by Julissa Bermudez.
Make It Happen is a 2008 American dance film directed by
Darren Grant and starring Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
The screenplay was co-written by Duane Adler, who was a screenwriter
for other dance films Step Up and Save the Last Dance.
Though the film was theatrically released internationally, the film was
released direct-to-video in the United States on December 9, 2008.
The film received generally negative reviews, with chief criticisms being that it was yet another
by-the-numbers dance film, though Winstead's performance received significant praise.
The film was also a commercial failure, only grossing $10 million.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.